{
    "maxRetryCount": 5,
    "triviaQuestions": [
        {
            "compatibleWith": [ "Imyt" ],
            "correctAnswers": [ true ],
            "id": "n4f3qsqpzzqh",
            "question": "InternetBound is Imyt's simp.",
            "type": "boolean"
        },
        {
            "compatibleWith": [ "Oatsngoats" ],
            "correctAnswers": [ true ],
            "id": "t0YkaoJkNSoy",
            "question": "InternetBound is Oats's simp.",
            "type": "boolean"
        },
        {
            "compatibleWith": [ "Imyt" ],
            "correctAnswers": [ true ],
            "id": "ljlq4yo7sowj",
            "question": "Imyt should get a free sippy blast.",
            "type": "boolean"
        },
        {
            "compatibleWith": [ "Imyt" ],
            "correctAnswers": [ "Eddie", "gaR", "Imyt", "InternetBound", "smCharles", "stashiocat" ],
            "id": "innb6nrtudrx",
            "question": "Who amongst the following people is a bully?",
            "responses": [ "Eddie", "gaR", "Imyt", "InternetBound", "smCharles", "stashiocat" ],
            "type": "multiple"
        },
        {
            "correctAnswers": [ true ],
            "id": "ftdpl5ja3kst",
            "question": "A fork is the best utensil for sushi.",
            "type": "boolean"
        },
        {
            "correctAnswers": [ "with ketchup and a coke" ],
            "id": "xazoikjjveqe",
            "question": "What is the proper way to eat a steak?",
            "responses": [ "with mayo", "well done", "fully cooked", "with ketchup and a coke", "steak is for the birds" ],
            "type": "multiple"
        },
        {
            "compatibleWith": [ "Imyt" ],
            "correctAnswers": [ true ],
            "id": "j0qwz2ji91tl",
            "question": "Imyt was once a hot tub streamer.",
            "type": "boolean"
        },
        {
            "correctAnswers": [ "Stashio" ],
            "id": "fphmdhkp0z1s",
            "question": "What is the name of stashiocat's pet cat?",
            "responses": [ "Mandoo", "Stashio", "Garfield", "Mozart", "Sassy", "Pepita" ],
            "type": "multiple"
        },
        {
            "correctAnswers": [ "Mandoo" ],
            "id": "qsvup6nmb2or",
            "question": "What is the name of Eddie's pet dog?",
            "responses": [ "Mandoo", "Stashio", "Air Bud", "Beethoven", "Chance", "Comet" ],
            "type": "multiple"
        },
        {
            "compatibleWith": [ "Imyt" ],
            "correctAnswers": [ "falling into vileplumes" ],
            "id": "a7l7hasy6qht",
            "question": "What is Nevdi most known for?",
            "responses": [ "falling into vileplumes", "perfect draygon fights", "good super rng", "bad phantoon patterns", "world's first PRKD 41" ],
            "type": "multiple"
        },
        {
            "compatibleWith": [ "Imyt" ],
            "correctAnswers": [ "izzy" ],
            "id": "cbgkj9utd2wp",
            "question": "Who is known for cooking hotdogs better than just about everyone?",
            "responses": [ "izzy", "Imyt", "Gordon Ramsay", "Guy Fieri", "Emeril Lagasse" ],
            "type": "multiple"
        },
        {
            "compatibleWith": [ "Imyt" ],
            "correctAnswers": [ "an entire suburb" ],
            "id": "ldduw4dgoewd",
            "question": "What could a single chimpanzee take out?",
            "responses": [ "an entire suburb", "not even a cat", "an anaconda", "a hippo", "a grizzly bear" ],
            "type": "multiple"
        },
        {
            "compatibleWith": [ "Imyt" ],
            "correctAnswers": [ true, false ],
            "id": "2jhqepcgegfa",
            "question": "A single human can fight a grizzly bear with a reasonable chance of winning.",
            "type": "boolean"
        },
        {
            "correctAnswers": [ true ],
            "id": "fixlbcgnpk2c",
            "question": "The bidet is the optimal human-interface device.",
            "type": "boolean"
        },
        {
            "compatibleWith": [ "Imyt" ],
            "correctAnswers": [ true ],
            "id": "fengbrjccaof",
            "question": "In an average year, Imyt goes on at least 1 vacation each month.",
            "type": "boolean"
        },
        {
            "correctAnswers": [ true ],
            "id": "qwibvlyrljey",
            "question": "With an expensive meal, nothing beats an ice-cold Coca-Cola.",
            "type": "boolean"
        },
        {
            "correctAnswers": [ true ],
            "id": "D2r2kFuMNpKh",
            "question": "InternetBound once defeated a horse by placing a saddle on its back.",
            "type": "boolean"
        },
        {
            "correctAnswers": [ "staying on the ground" ],
            "id": "qXlcAFddsYOr",
            "question": "In NEStroid, what is the optimal way for a flying enemy to attack you?",
            "responses": [ "diving from above", "flanking from the rear", "staying on the ground" ],
            "type": "multiple"
        },
        {
            "compatibleWith": [ "Imyt" ],
            "correctAnswers": [ true ],
            "id": "ffXOxJwV8MNU",
            "question": "Imyt once hit Charles in the face during an intense game of Family Feud.",
            "type": "boolean"
        },
        {
            "compatibleWith": [ "Imyt" ],
            "correctAnswers": [ "FRAMES", "GRIMES" ],
            "id": "7PrJqhNLrOE0",
            "question": "Complete the following phrase: PICTURE ______",
            "responses": [ "CRIMES", "FRAMES", "GRIMES" ],
            "type": "multiple"
        },
        {
            "compatibleWith": [ "Imyt" ],
            "correctAnswers": [ true ],
            "id": "RvM8MrUE7yCj",
            "question": "Stashiocat once tried to break CynanBot after Charles explicitly said not to.",
            "type": "boolean"
        },
        {
            "compatibleWith": [ "Imyt" ],
            "correctAnswers": [ true ],
            "id": "XF0JuQOyEh2a",
            "question": "The most popular speedrun category for the SNES game Lethal Weapon is Shark dupe%.",
            "type": "boolean"
        },
        {
            "compatibleWith": [ "Imyt" ],
            "correctAnswers": [ "2019", "Stashiocat never stopped bullying" ],
            "id": "jN8Pac73Mlaq",
            "question": "What year did stashiocat retire from bullying?",
            "responses": [ "2017", "2019", "2020", "Stashiocat never stopped bullying" ],
            "type": "multiple"
        },
        {
            "compatibleWith": [ "Oatsngoats" ],
            "correctAnswers": [ "Butter", "Nut Sweat" ],
            "id": "e6hQTfEL7ws4",
            "question": "How did Oats's chair become stained?",
            "responses": [ "Butter", "Ketchup", "Nut Sweat", "Doritos" ],
            "type": "multiple"
        },
        {
            "compatibleWith": [ "Imyt", "Oatsngoats" ],
            "correctAnswers": [ false ],
            "id": "GK9QtLdfdumq",
            "question": "In the Imyt vs. Oats hot chip challenge, Imyt spit out the chip.",
            "type": "boolean"
        },
        {
            "correctAnswers": [ true ],
            "id": "JzggrtDgVylu",
            "question": "Being at the top of the cuteness leaderboard means you are a better person.",
            "type": "boolean"
        }
    ]
}
